Mobius, Inc. Records MS208
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Press materials, 1977 -- 2007; MS208.003; 30.4 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s)
  - Tantalus Returns Again, 1979; MS208.003.053.00029 (Box 53)
  - TIME, 1985; MS208.003.053.00030 (Box 53)
  - Danger, Addiction, Pleasure, 1985; MS208.003.053.00031 (Box 53)
  - Bongo Bongo-Bongo Bongo, 1985; MS208.003.053.00032 (Box 53)
  - Inside a Legend: Images of St. Joan, 1986; MS208.003.053.00033 (Box 53)
  - Orpheus, 1983; MS208.003.053.00034 (Box 53)
  - Son of Theater Invaders, MS208.003.053.00035 (Box 53)
  - The Seventh Belle Part 2, 1987; MS208.003.053.00036 (Box 53)
  - The House of Opposite, 1987; MS208.003.053.00037 (Box 53)
  - Pigs Feet and Marble Skies, 1995; MS208.003.053.00038 (Box 53)
  - Contagious ARTrages #6, 1994; MS208.003.053.00039 (Box 53)
  - Pigs Feet and Marble Skies/Persephone and Hades, 1994; MS208.003.053.00040 (Box 53)
  - Party Universe, 1993; MS208.003.053.00041 (Box 53)
  - ARTrages as Mobius hits puberty, 1990; MS208.003.053.00042 (Box 53)
  - Marjorie Morgan, 1999; MS208.003.053.00043 (Box 53)
  - Sound Art at Mobius, 1986; MS208.003.054.00001 (Box 54)
  - Bread and Puppet, MS208.003.054.00002 (Box 54)
  - 22 Years at Mobius, MS208.003.054.00003 (Box 54)
  - The End of the World Rehersal Words/Pictures, MS208.003.054.00004 (Box 54)
  - The End of the World Rehearsal Words/Pictures, MS208.003.054.00005 (Box 54)
  - Performance Originals, MS208.003.054.00006 (Box 54)
  - Performance Originals, MS208.003.054.00007 (Box 54)
  - Performance Originals, MS208.003.054.00008 (Box 54)
  - Performance Originals, MS208.003.054.00009 (Box 54)
  - Performance Originals, MS208.003.054.00010 (Box 54)
  - Performance Originals, 1977 -- 1978; MS208.003.054.00011 (Box 54)
  - Poster Mock Ups- Sound Art, MS208.003.054.00012 (Box 54)
  - Courtesy Signs, Directions, etc., MS208.003.054.00013 (Box 54)
  - Performance Originals, MS208.003.054.00014 (Box 54)
  - Calendars, 1980 -- 1983; MS208.003.054.00015 (Box 54)
  - Calendars, 1980; MS208.003.054.00016 (Box 54)
  - Calendars, 1977 -- 1978; MS208.003.054.00017 (Box 54)
  - Performance Originals, MS208.003.054.00018 (Box 54)
  - The End of the World, MS208.003.054.00019 (Box 54)
  - Persephone and Hades/Tantalus, MS208.003.054.00020 (Box 54)
  - Relative Conditions/Orpheus Poster Originals, 1983 -- 1984; MS208.003.055.00001 (Box 55)
  - Recombinanat #1/#2 Poster Originals, 1981 -- 1982; MS208.003.055.00002 (Box 55)
  - Amuserama Poster/Postcard Originals, 1991; MS208.003.055.00003 (Box 55)
  - Mix Master Poster Originals, 1990; MS208.003.055.00004 (Box 55)
  - Persephone and Hades #6 Photos/Poster Originals, 1985; MS208.003.055.00005 (Box 55)
  - Persephone and Hades Performance Photos, 1987 -- 1988; MS208.003.055.00006 (Box 55)
  - Persephone and Hades Poster Originals, 1980; MS208.003.055.00007 (Box 55)
  - Pleasure, Addiction, Danger Poster Originals, 1986; MS208.003.055.00008 (Box 55)
  - Tantalus 1 and 2 Poster Originals, 1979; MS208.003.055.00009 (Box 55)
  - Persephone and Hades #4 Poster Originals, 1983; MS208.003.055.00010 (Box 55)
  - MIFPA 1st International Festival of Performing Arts Posters, 2006; MS208.003.055.00011 (Box 55)
  - Persephone and Hades Poster Originals, 1984 -- 1988; MS208.003.055.00012 (Box 55)
  - Passing of Time/Persephone and Hades Poster Originals, 1982; MS208.003.055.00013 (Box 55)
  - Fundraising Poster Originals, 1986 -- 1995; MS208.003.055.00014 (Box 55)
  - Persephone and Hades Poster Originals #1, 1980; MS208.003.055.00015 (Box 55)
  - Performance: Rochester NY Poster Originals, MS208.003.055.00016 (Box 55)
  - The House Opposite Poster Originals, 1987; MS208.003.055.00017 (Box 55)
  - Time Against Time Poster Originals, MS208.003.055.00018 (Box 55)
  - Playabout Poster Originals, 1984; MS208.003.055.00019 (Box 55)
  - Critic of God Poster Originals, 1988; MS208.003.055.00020 (Box 55)
  - Sound Art Poster Originals, David Tudor and Logos Duo, 1986; MS208.003.055.00021 (Box 55)
  - Science Projects Poster Originals, 1987; MS208.003.055.00022 (Box 55)
  - Throw it in the Fire/Seventh Belle/WIP Poster Originals, 1987; MS208.003.055.00023 (Box 55)
  - In the Flesh/Touring/Before and After Science/Inside a Legend Poster Originals, 1986; MS208.003.055.00024 (Box 55)
  - Discrete Events Poster Originals, 1983; MS208.003.055.00025 (Box 55)
  - Blank Frank #1/#2 Poster Originals, 1981 -- 1982; MS208.003.055.00026 (Box 55)
  - Son of Theater Invaders Poster Originals, 1983; MS208.003.055.00027 (Box 55)
  - Sleep A Thon T Shirt Design, 1996; MS208.003.055.00028 (Box 55)
  - Mobius 25 and Separated at Birth posters, 2003; MS208.003.055.00029 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 1)
    poster
  - Scrapbook, 1978 -- 1982; MS208.003.105.00002 (Box MS208 Shared 1)
    scrapbooks
  - Program and postcard archive, 1992 -- 1999; MS208.003.108 (Box 108)
  - Promotional material and artist biographies, 1993 -- 2006; MS208.003.109 (Box 109)
- Project files, 1975 -- 2005; MS208.004; 21.6 Linear Feet
  Project files documenting individual works, 1977-2006; and Mobius Performance Group (MPG) and Mobius Artist Group (MAG) touring files, circa 1985-1995. Generally, each work has a single project file, and includes the artist's resume or portfolio, project proposal, correspondence with Mobius, postcards and promotional materials, programs, and ticket sales statistics.
  - Artist Index and Newsletters, 1994 -- 1995; MS208.004.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Macedonia -- 1 of 5, 1994 -- 1995; MS208.004.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Macedonia -- 2 of 5, 1994 -- 1995; MS208.004.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Macedonia -- 3 of 5, 1994 -- 1995; MS208.004.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Macedonia -- 4 of 5, 1994 -- 1995; MS208.004.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Events/Scheduling, 1994 -- 1995; MS208.004.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Proposal Rejections, 1994; MS208.004.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Proposal Rejections, 1994; MS208.004.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Lincoln Ctr Out of Doors, 1994; MS208.004.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - David Peck "Expansions", 1990 -- 1994; MS208.004.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Mothers of Time, 1994; MS208.004.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Susan Dibble "The Man + the Angel" and "The Body Reveals", 1994; MS208.004.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Fort Point Open Studios, 1994; MS208.004.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Movement Works in Progress #5, 1994; MS208.004.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - MAG Sampler, 1994; MS208.004.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Exiles @ Mobius, 1994; MS208.004.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Outsider Quartet, 1994; MS208.004.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Andrew Neumann, 1994; MS208.004.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Margaret Titlemore "Drawn to It", 1994; MS208.004.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Taylor McLean "The Estevanico Cycle" Parts I, II, III, 1994; MS208.004.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Mari Novotny-Jones "Exact Location of the Soul", 1994; MS208.004.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Image Lab Observatory, 1994; MS208.004.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Contagious ARTrages, 1994; MS208.004.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Linda Graetz "Great Wall of Art", 1994; MS208.004.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - World AIDS Day, 1994; MS208.004.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Atlas/Axis "Permanent Record", 1994; MS208.004.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Works in Progress #36, 1994; MS208.004.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - N. Noon Coda, 1994 -- 1995; MS208.004.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Open Studios, 1987; MS208.004.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Betty Fain Dancers, 1987; MS208.004.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - CCAE -- MPG, 1987; MS208.004.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Paula Hunter, 1987; MS208.004.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Taylor McLean, 1988; MS208.004.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Sound-Image-Events, 1987; MS208.004.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - After First Death, 1987; MS208.004.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Eva Dean Dance Co., 1987; MS208.004.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - House Opposite, 1987; MS208.004.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Deborah Boardman Stations of Mary, 1988; MS208.004.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Theater Works-In-Progress, 1988; MS208.004.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - W.I.P., 1988; MS208.004.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Silvia Gruner, 1988; MS208.004.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Blue Mon -- Nancy Adams, 1988; MS208.004.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - WIP #25, 1988; MS208.004.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Sylvia Gruner - via O DePaso, 1988; MS208.004.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Mega-Scan -- T.W.LI, 1988; MS208.004.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - P + H, 1988; MS208.004.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Clean Break/tech, etc., 1988; MS208.004.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Clean Break, 1988; MS208.004.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Marilyn Gottlieb-Roberts, 1987 -- 1989; MS208.004.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Student Proposals, 1988; MS208.004.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - MPG@Zone, 1988; MS208.004.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - AIDS Show, 1988; MS208.004.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Little Feats, 1988; MS208.004.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Critic of God, 1988; MS208.004.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Instrumentalia, 1988; MS208.004.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Pacific Transducer Series, 1988; MS208.004.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Bojidar Pinek, 1988; MS208.004.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - 7 Yellow Actions, South Shore Arts, 1988; MS208.004.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Frank Vasello, 1988; MS208.004.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Little Feats of Daring, 1988; MS208.004.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Critic of God, Lang, 1988; MS208.004.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Installation Project, 1988; MS208.004.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Interns, 1988 -- 1989; MS208.004.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Submerge -- Mary Fleming, 1988; MS208.004.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Taylor McLean, 1988; MS208.004.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - Open Studios, 1988; MS208.004.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - WIP #26, 1988; MS208.004.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Elizabeth Witham, 1988; MS208.004.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - Bones and Bones, 1988; MS208.004.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - Misc. Posters + Postcards, 1989; MS208.004.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - Of Tanne, 1987; MS208.004.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - Terrain II/Blades of Grass, 1989; MS208.004.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - Mobius Sampler, 1988; MS208.004.009.00045 (Box 9)
  - No Meaning/Taking Stock Rochester, 1988; MS208.004.009.00046 (Box 9)
  - Hikari, 1988 -- 1989; MS208.004.009.00047 (Box 9)
  - Meredith Davis -- Where the Wild Geese Fly, 1989; MS208.004.009.00048 (Box 9)
  - Of Tanne, 1989; MS208.004.009.00049 (Box 9)
  - Marilyn Arsem -- Sculpture (Mobius at) Space, 1989; MS208.004.009.00050 (Box 9)
  - Lindy Annis, 1989; MS208.004.009.00051 (Box 9)
  - Broadcast Live, 1989; MS208.004.009.00052 (Box 9)
  - Domestic Triology, 1989; MS208.004.009.00053 (Box 9)
  - Tim Martin, 1989; MS208.004.009.00054 (Box 9)
  - Theaterworks, 1989; MS208.004.009.00055 (Box 9)
  - WIP #27, 1989; MS208.004.009.00056 (Box 9)
  - Johnson/Osborn, 1988; MS208.004.009.00057 (Box 9)
  - Prairie Dog Seance, 1989; MS208.004.009.00058 (Box 9)
  - Collaborations Panel, 1989; MS208.004.009.00059 (Box 9)
  - Hannah Bonner, 1989; MS208.004.009.00060 (Box 9)
  - Drought, 1989; MS208.004.009.00061 (Box 9)
  - Student Works, 1989; MS208.004.009.00062 (Box 9)
  - Easterly/Current Dance Co., 1989; MS208.004.009.00063 (Box 9)
  - Terrain, 1989; MS208.004.009.00064 (Box 9)
  - WIP #28, 1989; MS208.004.009.00065 (Box 9)
  - Landon Rose, 1995; MS208.004.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Neil Leonard, Ean White, 1995; MS208.004.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Joseph Wilson, 1995; MS208.004.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Caleb Brown, 1995; MS208.004.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Debris, 1995; MS208.004.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - T Max + Izzy Maxwell, 1995; MS208.004.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Erik Edson, 1995; MS208.004.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Student Works, 1995; MS208.004.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Askansas/Vance, 1995; MS208.004.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Move WIP, 1995; MS208.004.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Milan Kohout, Mari N-J, 1995; MS208.004.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Charles Goss, 1995; MS208.004.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Meg Gilman, 1995; MS208.004.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - S.H.i.P.S., 1995; MS208.004.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Sandy Goldberg, 1995; MS208.004.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Taylor McLean, 1995; MS208.004.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Voigt/Barnum, 1995; MS208.004.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Cage Project, 1995; MS208.004.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Teens Show Teens Show, 1995; MS208.004.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - Cathy Nolan, 1995; MS208.004.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - P&H, 1995; MS208.004.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - WIP #37, 1995; MS208.004.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - MAG Works, 1995; MS208.004.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - Susan Graham, 1995; MS208.004.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - CANCELLED -- Caitlin Corbett, 1995; MS208.004.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - Mobius - Macedonia, 1995 -- 1996; MS208.004.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - Macedonia Contacts, Gen. Corresp., 1995 -- 1996; MS208.004.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Mala Stanica - Boston, 1995 -- 1996; MS208.004.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - Mala Stanica, 1995 -- 1996; MS208.004.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Macedonia, 1995 -- 1996; MS208.004.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - Artist Index and Newsletters, 1995 -- 1996; MS208.004.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Liquor Amnii Info (Prep for Rept), 1998; MS208.004.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - Macedonia Proj $, 1996 -- 1997; MS208.004.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - Liquor Amnii cont., 1996 -- 1997; MS208.004.010.00034 (Box 10)
  - Liquor Amnii Slides, 1996 -- 1997; MS208.004.010.00035 (Box 10)
  - Resumes -- Convergence, 1997; MS208.004.010.00036 (Box 10)
  - Macedonia Brochure, 1997; MS208.004.010.00037 (Box 10)
  - Liquor Amnii -- Cuseeme event, 1997; MS208.004.010.00038 (Box 10)
  - NYC, 1997; MS208.004.010.00039 (Box 10)
  - Travel -- Convergence, 1997; MS208.004.010.00040 (Box 10)
  - Macedonia Proj Site Research -- Convergence, 1997; MS208.004.010.00041 (Box 10)
  - Project Descriptions -- Convergence, 1997; MS208.004.010.00042 (Box 10)
  - PR/Schedules -- Convergence, 1997; MS208.004.010.00043 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence -- Convergence, 1997; MS208.004.010.00044 (Box 10)
  - MAG Survey, 1996; MS208.004.010.00045 (Box 10)
  - Dadaist Poems (1 of 2), 1996; MS208.004.010.00046 (Box 10)
  - Dadaist Poems (2 of 2), 1996; MS208.004.010.00047 (Box 10)
  - Mag, 1995 -- 1996; MS208.004.010.00048 (Box 10)
  - Non-Mag, 1995 -- 1996; MS208.004.010.00049 (Box 10)
  - Rejection Letters, 1995 -- 1996; MS208.004.010.00050 (Box 10)
  - Titlemore -- Red Shoes, 1995; MS208.004.010.00051 (Box 10)
  - Frank Vasello, 1995; MS208.004.010.00052 (Box 10)
  - Lansdowne Playhouse, 1995; MS208.004.010.00053 (Box 10)
  - Lansdowne Playhouse Benefit for Mobius, 1995; MS208.004.010.00054 (Box 10)
  - MAG Exhibit, 1995; MS208.004.010.00055 (Box 10)
  - MAG Sampler, 1995; MS208.004.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - George Fifield, 1995; MS208.004.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Daniel Orlansky, 1995; MS208.004.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - MWIP #7, 1995; MS208.004.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Fort Pt. Open Studios, 1995; MS208.004.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Cathy Nolan, 1995; MS208.004.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Taylor McLean, 1995; MS208.004.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Sharon Haggins Dunn, 1995; MS208.004.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Gaduri, 1995; MS208.004.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Day of Dead, 1995; MS208.004.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Arsem/davis/Graetz @ Hera Gallery, RI, 1995; MS208.004.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - George Fifield, 1995; MS208.004.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - WIP #38, 1995; MS208.004.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Jed Speare, 1995; MS208.004.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Svjetlana Bukvic, 1995; MS208.004.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - World AIDS Day, 1995; MS208.004.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Laura Evans, 1995; MS208.004.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Mari Novotny-Jones & Milan Kohout, 1995; MS208.004.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Susan L. Baltazer, 1996; MS208.004.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - R.L. McIntosh, 1996; MS208.004.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Caitlin Corbett + Dance Company, 1996; MS208.004.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - George Fifield, VideoSpace, 1996; MS208.004.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - "No Bias", 1996; MS208.004.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Neil Leonard, 1996; MS208.004.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - VideoSpace, 1996; MS208.004.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Movement WIP, 1998; MS208.004.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - Ellen Band, 1996; MS208.004.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - Larry Johnson, 1996; MS208.004.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Stephanie Cohen, 1996; MS208.004.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - Student Works, 1996; MS208.004.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - Zaporah Ruth Owen Furshpan & Sarah hickler, 1996; MS208.004.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - VideoSpace, 1996; MS208.004.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - Arthur Hardigg, 1996; MS208.004.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - Meredith Davis, 1996; MS208.004.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - Tom Plsek/David Miller, 1996; MS208.004.011.00035 (Box 11)
  - Cathy Nolan, 1996; MS208.004.011.00036 (Box 11)
  - Decastro, Fifield, Johnson, Laffoley, Walker, Windra -- UFO, 1996; MS208.004.011.00037 (Box 11)
  - W.I.P., 1996; MS208.004.011.00038 (Box 11)
  - VideoSpace, 1996; MS208.004.011.00039 (Box 11)
  - Joe Wilson, 1996; MS208.004.011.00040 (Box 11)
  - Collab. Panel, 1996; MS208.004.011.00041 (Box 11)
  - Sheila Pepe, 1996; MS208.004.011.00042 (Box 11)
  - Mari Novotny -- Jones + D. Miller, 1996; MS208.004.011.00043 (Box 11)
  - Jed Speare Performance in Video, 1996; MS208.004.011.00044 (Box 11)
  - Marjorie Morgan, 1996; MS208.004.011.00045 (Box 11)
  - VideoSpace, 1996; MS208.004.011.00046 (Box 11)
  - Billie Jo Joy, 1996; MS208.004.011.00047 (Box 11)
  - Todd, Chang, Rowling, 1996; MS208.004.011.00048 (Box 11)
  - Collaboration -- MAG, 1996; MS208.004.011.00049 (Box 11)
  - MAG Collab., 1996; MS208.004.011.00050 (Box 11)
  - Art a la Carte, 1996; MS208.004.011.00051 (Box 11)
  - T. Plsek/GYBSO, 1996; MS208.004.011.00052 (Box 11)
  - Artist Index and Newsletters, 1996 -- 1997; MS208.004.011.00053 (Box 11)
  - Teaching @ Mobius, MS208.004.011.00054 (Box 11)
  - Macedonia Bath Xchange Corresp., MS208.004.011.00055 (Box 11)
  - MAG Scheduling + Non-MAG, 1996 -- 1997; MS208.004.011.00056 (Box 11)
  - Rejections, Proposal Review, 1996; MS208.004.011.00057 (Box 11)
  - No Bias, 1996; MS208.004.011.00058 (Box 11)
  - Wilson Keefe O'Brien, 1996; MS208.004.011.00059 (Box 11)
  - BCFE, 1996; MS208.004.011.00060 (Box 11)
  - BCFE, 1996; MS208.004.011.00061 (Box 11)
  - Haggins-Dunn, 1996; MS208.004.011.00062 (Box 11)
  - Riskin, Seth NOA Gemini, 1996; MS208.004.011.00063 (Box 11)
  - Voigt/Licata, 1996; MS208.004.011.00064 (Box 11)
  - Sampler, 1996; MS208.004.011.00065 (Box 11)
  - Open Studios, 1996; MS208.004.011.00066 (Box 11)
  - VideoSpace/Fifield Halloween Show, 1996; MS208.004.011.00067 (Box 11)
  - Movement WIP #8, 1996; MS208.004.011.00068 (Box 11)
  - Rejected Proposals, 1996; MS208.004.011.00069 (Box 11)
  - Sasha Bergman, 1996; MS208.004.011.00070 (Box 11)
  - Jed Speare, 1996; MS208.004.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Greenberg Birdsong of Mesozoic, 1996; MS208.004.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Macedonian Slides, 1996; MS208.004.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Kohout, 1996; MS208.004.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Rose/Graetz, 1996; MS208.004.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - ArtRages, 1996; MS208.004.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - VideoSpace Irony Rules, 1996; MS208.004.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Marsching, 1996; MS208.004.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Arsem Stirring/Spinning/Sweeping, 1996; MS208.004.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - VideoSpace reconstructions, 1999; MS208.004.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - D. Franklin, 1996; MS208.004.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - M. Tittemore, 1997; MS208.004.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - noon coda, 1997; MS208.004.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - VideoSpace California Video, 1997; MS208.004.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Miller/Rose/Johnson/Speare, 1997; MS208.004.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Carol Greenwood "of Substance", 1997; MS208.004.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - "The Berlin Wall" Novotny Jones-Kohout, 1997; MS208.004.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Student Works, 1997; MS208.004.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Snyder Tor, Title: 7th generation ensemble, 1997; MS208.004.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - St. Susan Baltozer "the uncertainty of belief", 1997; MS208.004.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Arthur Handigg "Fruit Jam", 1997; MS208.004.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Student Works, 1997; MS208.004.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Brian Crabtree "the problem dances", 1997; MS208.004.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - VideoSpace Student Show, 1997; MS208.004.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - VideoSpace New Ground, 1997; MS208.004.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - Vivianne Le Courtois-Mitchell, Kombusha World, 1997; MS208.004.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - Debris -- Dance "Hubris", 1997; MS208.004.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - WIP #40, 1997; MS208.004.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - Elegy, 1997; MS208.004.012.00029 (Box 12)
  - VideoSpace: Mr. and Mrs. Zone, Again, 1997; MS208.004.012.00030 (Box 12)
  - MAG WIP, 1997; MS208.004.012.00031 (Box 12)
  - Taylor McLean, 1997; MS208.004.012.00032 (Box 12)
  - Berlin Wall III, 1997; MS208.004.012.00033 (Box 12)
  - Maureen Albano "Insatiable appetite to please", 1997; MS208.004.012.00034 (Box 12)
  - Light Housekeeping/Chorus Angelorum, 1997; MS208.004.012.00035 (Box 12)
  - VideoSpace Ungreased Videos, 1997; MS208.004.012.00036 (Box 12)
  - Guadelesa "Leap of Faith", 1997; MS208.004.012.00037 (Box 12)
  - William Pope L. "Eracism", 1997; MS208.004.012.00038 (Box 12)
  - Teens Show, 1997; MS208.004.012.00039 (Box 12)
  - Lise Brody + Marjorie Morgan "Salt", 1997; MS208.004.012.00040 (Box 12)
  - Liquor Amnii, 1997; MS208.004.012.00041 (Box 12)
  - Liquor Amnii, Convergence Festival, RI, 1997; MS208.004.012.00042 (Box 12)
  - Teen Show, 1997; MS208.004.012.00043 (Box 12)
  - Proposal Reject Letters, 1997; MS208.004.012.00044 (Box 12)
  - FDNH, 1997; MS208.004.012.00045 (Box 12)
  - Mobius at DeCordova, 1997; MS208.004.012.00046 (Box 12)
  - Artist Index, 1997 -- 1998; MS208.004.012.00047 (Box 12)
  - Matt Samolis, 1997; MS208.004.012.00048 (Box 12)
  - Ross Hamlin, 1997; MS208.004.012.00049 (Box 12)
  - Sampler, 1997; MS208.004.012.00050 (Box 12)
  - VideoSpace, 1997; MS208.004.012.00051 (Box 12)
  - Tom Plsek, 1997; MS208.004.012.00052 (Box 12)
  - Group Show: Zen Dada, 1997; MS208.004.012.00053 (Box 12)
  - Mobius at ICA, 1997; MS208.004.012.00054 (Box 12)
  - Sharon Dunn, 1997; MS208.004.012.00055 (Box 12)
  - Ann Carson, 1997; MS208.004.012.00056 (Box 12)
  - Boston Fire Department, 1997; MS208.004.012.00057 (Box 12)
  - No-Thank-U Letters, 1997; MS208.004.012.00058 (Box 12)
  - Rejection Letters, 1997; MS208.004.012.00059 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous Rentals, 1997 -- 1998; MS208.004.012.00060 (Box 12)
  - Mailing List Prices, 1996 -- 1998; MS208.004.012.00061 (Box 12)
  - Mailing List Exchanges Purchases + Sale Contracts, 1990 -- 1995; MS208.004.012.00062 (Box 12)
  - Caroline Baganel, 1997; MS208.004.012.00063 (Box 12)
  - Contracts and Rental Agreements (1 of 2), 1990 -- 1996; MS208.004.012.00064 (Box 12)
  - Contracts and Rental Agreements (2 of 2), 1983 -- 1990; MS208.004.012.00065 (Box 12)
  - experimental TV, 1997; MS208.004.012.00066 (Box 12)
  - D. Miller, 1997; MS208.004.012.00067 (Box 12)
  - Taylor McLean, 1997; MS208.004.012.00068 (Box 12)
  - Whitney Bound -- Rob Abate et al, 1997; MS208.004.012.00069 (Box 12)
  - Violeta Simjanovska presentation, 1997; MS208.004.012.00070 (Box 12)
  - VideoSpace:, 1997; MS208.004.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - M. Tittemore, 1997; MS208.004.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - W.I.P., 1997; MS208.004.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - VideoSpace:, 1997; MS208.004.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Caleb Brown, 1997; MS208.004.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Creative Expressions Boston Poetry, 1997; MS208.004.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Karen Gilg, 1998; MS208.004.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Berlin Wall IV, 1998; MS208.004.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - VideoSpace, 1998; MS208.004.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Text + Sound II, 1998; MS208.004.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Julia Szabo, 1998; MS208.004.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - A Hole in My Heart, Julia Szabo, 1998; MS208.004.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - VideoSpace Found/Stolen Videos, 1998; MS208.004.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Sharon Dunn, 1998; MS208.004.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - The Footsteps of AREPO, 1998; MS208.004.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - ICA Stay, 1998; MS208.004.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Larry Johnson, 1998; MS208.004.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Student Works, 1998; MS208.004.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - VideoSpace, 1998; MS208.004.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Abbie Conant, 1998; MS208.004.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Tony Carruthers, 1998; MS208.004.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Meredith Davis, 1998; MS208.004.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - Barbara Poole, 1998; MS208.004.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - Megg Cottam, Stork, 1998; MS208.004.013.00024 (Box 13)